[
    {
        "question": "Which of the following taxes is a progressive tax?",
        "choice1": "Income Tax",
        "choice2": "Custom Tax",
        "choice3": "Sales Tax",
        "choice4": "Excise Duty",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Find the mean of 8, 3, 5, 2, 7, 5, 7, 3, 6, 7.",
        "choice1": "5.1",
        "choice2": "5.2",
        "choice3": "5.3",
        "choice4": "5.4",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Find the mode of the followwing set of numbers: 2, 6, 7, 6, 8, 5, 2, 4, 2, 4, 5.",
        "choice1": "2",
        "choice2": "4",
        "choice3": "5",
        "choice4": "7",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Find the median of the following percentage: 43%, 76%, 64%, 37%, 76%, 54%.",
        "choice1": "64%",
        "choice2": "54%",
        "choice3": "118%",
        "choice4": "59%",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "A demand curve can shift because of changing...",
        "choice1": "Income",
        "choice2": "Prices of related goods",
        "choice3": "Taste",
        "choice4": "All of the above",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "If your income during one year is N10,000 and the following year is N12,000, then it has increased by?",
        "choice1": "20%",
        "choice2": "2%",
        "choice3": "12%",
        "choice4": "16%",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "When total utility reaches its maximum, then marginal utility will be...",
        "choice1": "Minimum",
        "choice2": "Average",
        "choice3": "Zero",
        "choice4": "Negative",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following taxes is a progressive tax?",
        "choice1": "Custom Tax",
        "choice2": "Income Tax",
        "choice3": "Sales Tax",
        "choice4": "Excise Duty",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "A supply curve is directly affected by?",
        "choice1": "Technology",
        "choice2": "Input Costs",
        "choice3": "Government Regulations",
        "choice4": "All of the above",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "Other things being equal, what causes a decrease in demand?",
        "choice1": "Rise in the price of the substitute",
        "choice2": "Fall in the price of the commodity",
        "choice3": "Rise in the income of the consumer",
        "choice4": "Rise in the price of the commodity",
        "answer": 4
    }
]